directspecialstoday.com 2013-06-05

# Direct Specials Today

CSS transforms are not supported in your browser

CSS transitions are not supported in your browser Sorry, only modern browsers.

Last Revised: October 1, 2009

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Direct Specials Today ("Direct Specials Today" "we" or "us") with respect to your use of our Web site located at www.directspecialstoday.com (the "Site") so you can make an informed decision about using our Site. By using our Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy, as may be modified by us from time to time.We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the privacy policy the date it was last updated. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes or revised statement shall constitute your consent to any changes in our privacy practices. We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you visit our Site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Collection And Use Of Personal Information

**Active Collection:** Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site. We may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name, email address, and other contact information when you register and set up an account or contact us by e-mail or other means through the Site. Personal and demographic information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with submitting a review, posting comments or other content, creating a profile or group, applying for a job, sending an email or message to another user or participating in any interactive forums or features on the Site. In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities that may appear form time to time on the Site.

**Passive Collection:** When you use the Site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and your activity on the Site. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only. 

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons. Cookies are small data files that are stored on a user's hard drive at the request of a Web site to enable the site to recognize users who have previously visited them and retain certain information such as customer preferences and history. If we link cookies to any personally identifying information, we will treat this information as personal information. Web beacons (also know as clear gifs) are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Site or in emails relating to the Site to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Site. We may also use third parties to serve ads or content on the Site, and such third parties may place cookies, web beacons or other devices on your computer to collect nonpersonal information.

The information provided by these cookies, web beacons and other devices may include data about users' activities online and may be used to, among other things, analyze data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other sites tracked by us and these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or web beacons in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology.

If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser manufacturer to learn about these functions. However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Site may not function properly.

## How Do We Use The Personal Information We Collect?

In general, we use personal information we collect to: process your requests or transactions; provide you with information, products or services you request; inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you; facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site; and for the purpose for which the information was provided. For example, we may use the information we collect to: 

  * send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Site, to provide other services, products or information you request and to complete any transactions in connection therewith;
  * respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;
  * request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications, products and services;
  * analyze data and trends and to personalize and improve site content and features and your experience on the Site and on third party sites we partner with, such as providing ads, content or features tailored to match your profile and interests; and
  * contact you about our or a third party’s services, products, activities, special events or offers, and for other internal marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes.

Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our services and those of our partners. In addition, if we receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you.

## Information Sharing Or Disclosure

In the event that we contract with a third party to provide some part of the information or service that you have requested, Direct Specials Today may provide your information to such third party, or such third party may collect information from you on our behalf. By written agreement, these third parties are required to implement similar security measures and to process your information only as authorized by Direct Specials Today to fulfill the service(s) that they have been contracted to provide. Other than these entities, who act on our behalf, information you provide at this site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties, unless we have your permission to do so. However, please note that personal information provided to this site may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders.

## What Personal Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through this Site with third parties except as described in this Policy, as it may be revised from time to time. We may share personal information with vendors, consultants and other service providers ("Service Providers") who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Site or the services we provide and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us. In some cases, the Service Provider may be directly collecting the information from you on our behalf. We may also share personal information with other third parties when you give us your consent to do so. We are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these Service Providers or other third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them. Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregate information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent.

We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Direct Specials Today, our users, our employees or the public, including without limitation to protect Direct Specials Today or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate or unlawful use of our Site. Information about our users, including personal information, may also be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of Direct Specials Today.

You understand that when you use the Site, information you post in your profile, reviews, forums and other interactive areas of the Site, as well as any information you share with individuals through the Site, will be available to other users and in some cases may be publicly available. We recommend you be cautious about giving out personal information to others or sharing personal information in public or private online forums. We are not responsible for the actions of any third parties with whom you share personal information.

We may also share information about your online activities with third parties in order to help such third parties improve your experience on their sites, to allow such third parties to analyze data and trends and to personalize and improve their site content and features and deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests. Such information typically does not include personal information unless we first get your consent to share such personal information.

## What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online?

We have endeavored to put into place and maintain reasonable security measures in an effort to protect the security of your personal information while it is under our control. For example, your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our web site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. Please note that we store only encrypted passwords, so even our employees can not recover your password.

## What Choices Do You Have Regarding The Use Of Your Information?

You may "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional communications from us, through links provided with every such communication or through account preferences on the website. Please note that this will not affect our ability to send you service and account related emails or to use your personal information as otherwise described in this Policy.

## Links To Other Web Sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of web sites to which we link. Links from our web site to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

## How Can You Correct and Update Your Personal Information or Obtain Additional Information

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or the practices relating to this Site, or you wish to verify, correct or delete any personal information we have collected, please contact us at feedback@directspecialstoday.com and we will endeavor to respond to your inquiry or to correct, update or remove the personal information you have provided us as you indicate. You may also contact us by mail at the following address:

Direct Specials Today Attn: Privacy Policy 3435 Ocean Park Blvd. #107 PMB 319 Santa Monica, CA 90405 

However, please note that in some cases, we may believe it is necessary or appropriate to retain certain personal information we have collected, and the deletion of such personal information will be in our sole discretion unless otherwise required by law.
